https://childrensgroup.com/privacy-policy-2/

The Mozart Effect Products
The Mozart Effect: Live!
Other Brands
Yo Gabba Gabba: Music is Awesome!
The Mozart Effect Products
The Mozart Effect: Live!
Other Brands
Yo Gabba Gabba: Music is Awesome!
The Mozart Effect Products
The Mozart Effect: Live!
Other Brands
Yo Gabba Gabba: Music is Awesome!
The Mozart Effect Products
The Mozart Effect: Live!
Other Brands
Yo Gabba Gabba: Music is Awesome!
Privacy Policy
This policy applies to The Children’s Group. At The Children’s Group, the security and integrity of our customers’ personal information is important to us. We take every reasonable measure necessary to protect the privacy of our customers while providing the high level communication services they expect.Our privacy practices are in accordance with all federal and provincial laws and regulations. We are compliant with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (“PIPEDA”). As part of this commitment, we have adopted the Principles established by the Canadian Standards Association’s Model Code for the protection of Personal Information and similar provincial laws, which establish rules governing the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information by the private sector. Our Privacy Principles: Accountability: All employees of The Children’s Group Inc. are responsible for maintaining and protecting all Personal Information under their control. The Children’s Group Inc. has designated an individual to oversee the company’s compliance with the Act and our Privacy Principles (Privacy Officer, The Children’s Group Inc., 1815 Ironstone Manor, Suite 13, Pickering, Ontario, L1W 3W9. Identifying Purposes: We will identify the purposes for which Personal Information is collected, either before or at the time of collection. Consent: The cornerstone to protecting your privacy is consent. We will only collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information with your consent, except where otherwise permitted or required by law.  Consent can be express or it may be implied in appropriate circumstances. Express Consent can be given by you in writing, in person, electronically, by telephone, or by using a check-off box. Implied Consent may be used by us as a basis for extending new marketing offers or delivering catalogs to you. We will not use your implied consent for the use or disclosure of your sensitive Personal Information such as financial data.  Withdrawing Consent: You may withdraw your consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. If you withdraw your consent, we will inform you of the implications of such withdrawal. To withdraw your consent, simply contact us and advise us of what Personal Information you no longer wish us to use.  You may choose not to provide us with any of your Personal Information. Personal Information is broadly defined as information about an identifiable individual, but does not include the name, title, business address, or telephone number of an employee of an organization. The ‘Act’ also doesn’t cover the collection, use or disclosure of personal information solely for journalistic, artistic or literary purposes. Data we collect with personal identifiers removed, so that it is impossible to determine the identity of the person whom the information relates, is not considered Personal Information.  Personal Information We Collect:  With your consent, we may collect Personal Information from you in person, over the telephone, by mail, through the Internet or from our selected third party service providers/business partners such as Chase Paymentech. The type of information we usually collect and maintain may include your:NameMailing/Billing street addressEmail AddressTelephone NumbersTransaction HistoryDate of Birth It is always your choice as to whether or not you provide us with your Personal Information; however, if you make this choice we may not be able to provide you with the product, service or information that you requested or that could be offered to you. Limiting Collection: We will limit the collection of your Personal Information to only those details that are necessary for the purposes identified. We may use your Personal Information to:identify you and communicate with you generallyprocess your orders and/or applicationsestablish and maintain a relationship with you, and to provide you with ongoing servicedevelop an understanding of your needs and eligibility for products and services and to bring you offersadminister contests and other promotionsprotect you, and us, against error and fraudadminister merchandise refunds/exchanges Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention: Your Personal Information will only be used or disclosed for the purpose for which it was collected, unless you have otherwise consented, or when it is required or permitted by law. We will only retain your Personal Information for the period of time required to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected. Accuracy: We will keep Personal Information we collect as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected. Security & Safeguards: The Children’s Group will protect personal information by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information, including through the use of the following measures: physical (e.g., locked filing cabinets, restricted access, appropriate disposal of personal information), organizational (e.g., security clearances, access only on a “need to know” basis), technological (e.g., passwords, encryption) and training of employees. Openness: Information about our policies and practices relating to the management of Personal Information will be made readily available to you. Access: At your request, we will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of your Personal Information, as well as give you access to the information. You have the right to challenge the accuracy and completeness of your information, and to amend it as necessary.Upon written request, you may access and verify your Personal Information and find out to whom we have disclosed it. At the time of your request, we will need specific information from you to verify your identity, before we can provide you with the Personal Information we hold.There may be instances when we will not be able to provide you with the Personal Information that you request. Examples are if the Personal Information:contains references to other personshas already been destroyed due to legal requirements or because we no longer needed it for our purposesis subject to solicitor-client or litigation privilegecannot be disclosed for other legal reasons Changing your Personal InformationWe are committed to maintaining the accuracy of your Personal Information for as long as it is being used for the purposes we have identified. To help us keep your Personal Information up-to-date, we encourage you to notify us of inaccuracies or corrections as often as you wish. Notification of changes such as your address or telephone number will help us provide you with the best possible service. If you identify any incorrect or outdated information requiring amendment, please contact us. We may ask you to put your request for a correction in writing. We will make the proper changes and, upon your request, provide you with a copy of the corrected information. Cookies and Log Files: Cookies are information files that your web browser places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user’s hard drive. Cookies are used to track visitor activities while at our site. The Children’s Group Inc. uses Cookies to determine the number of unique and returning visitors to our website. We do not store any personal information into cookies. Log data collected on web servers, both within our control and under the control of third party service providers, is used to identify IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitor movement to, through and from the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Links: This website contains links to other websites. The Children’s Group Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. Our Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website. Order Now and Order Products Links: Ordering services and order fulfillment for The Children’s Group Inc. products featured on our site are provided by unrelated third-party service providers through links to unrelated websites. While we make every effort to verify the integrity and ability of such service providers to provide ordering services and order fulfillment, The Children’s Group Inc. is not liable for the failure of such service providers to provide these services. The Children’s Group Inc. is not liable for the privacy practices of such service providers or sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. Our Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website. Surveys: Our website requests information from visitors via online surveys. Participation in these surveys is voluntary and visitors may choose whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information may be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our website and demographic information about our visitors. Parental Consent: Children under the age of 13 must have a parent’s (or legal guardian’s) permission to submit personal information. In the event of contest entries, children under the age of 13 must include a parents (or guardian’s) valid email address. Entries will not be accepted unless and until we have received verification of parental consent via return email by the response deadline date. Change of Policy Notices: We reserve the right to amend, modify, add or otherwise change our Privacy Policy. In the event of a material change in the collection, use or disclosure practices of The Children’s Group Inc., we will notify visitors to our site and recipients contained in our electronic newsletter email list. Challenging Compliance: You may contact us with any questions, complaints or suggestions with respect to the above principles.Privacy OfficerThe Children’s Group Inc.23 Griffin St.Waterdown, ON CANADA L0R 2H0Phone: (905) 690–9397Email: moreinfo@childrensgroup.co
